Christian Servillon Oxeniola

Blk 7 Lt 24 Springtown Villas, Brgy. Gaya-Gaya SJDM Bulacan 3023

+639566603741

EMAIL: oxeniolachristian@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To be a part of an organization where I could employ the experiences I have gained as a Virtual Assistant and in the BPO industry. To have more opportunities for growth while ensuring my contribution to the realization of the company's goals.

COMPETENCIES

Solid background in Customer Service, Technical Support and Email. Team management and analyzing performance and behavior. Proficient in Microsoft Office applications and spreadsheet. Superb experience with Amazon, Shopify and eBay as well as Facebook Ads & PPC.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Amazon | eBay | Shopify

eCommerce stores

Customer Support Rep | Social Media Manager | PPC & FB Ads Manager

August 2017 - January 2021

- > Primary responsibility is to help store owners to rank their product on Amazon and provide world class customer support.
- Running, Scaling and Managing Facebook ads
- Product listing on eBay, Shopify and Amazon
- Running and optimizing Amazon PPC
- Create and edit photos and videos using Canva and Photoshop
- > Product Research and creates chat flow and automation in ManyChat
- > Respond to email inquiries in Zendesk and Freshdesk making sure that our customers are happy and satisfied.
- > Utilizing Helium 10 mainly for Keyword Research and Tracking and Keyword Indexing and optimization.

CarToys Australia Incorporated

Mawson Lake, South Australia

Personal Virtual Assistant

August 2016 - 2017

- > Primary responsibility is to establish and maintain good relationship with source companies, manage appointment and schedules.
- > Product inventory and fulfillment
- Take measures to resolve Paypal and Stripe disputes
- > Organize team meeting and manage team members
- > Run Facebook Ads and submit product and market research
- ➤ Provide bi-weekly report to the owner regarding inventory, sales, current team performance, customer satisfaction rating, Ads cost and updates from company partners.

Convergys ComCast Account

UP Technohub, Commonwealth

Transition Team Leader

April 2012 - September 2016

- > Manage all the team who transitioned from training to production before they are distributed to their assigned team leaders.
- > Perform root cause analysis, formulate action plans and assess individual behaviors.
- > Provide individual weekly coaching to members of the team and collaborate in an action plan to increase efficiency and performance.
- > Direct and In-direct feedback to members of the team and follow up on the status of agreed action plan to attain a certain objective.
- > Accept call escalations and provide appropriate resolution.
- Provide bi-weekly report to Operations Manager and monthly report to Senior Operations Manager regarding the team performance, action plans and agent behaviors and profiles.

Subject Matter Expert

July 2011 - April 2012

- Assist the transition team leader in organizing half of the team.
- > Answer questions and inquiries from members of the team and provide assistance on tools usage and troubleshooting.
- > Provide daily feedback and update on individual performance.
- > Weekly report to Transition Team Leader on cluster's performance and propose action plans.

Technical Support Representative

November 2009 - July 2011

- > Troubleshoot internet and cable tv issues and dispatch technicians if needed.
- Answer billing inquiries and analyze disputes
- > Sales Pitch for all resolve issues or discuss any eligible promotions

Certificates and Recognition

- ➤ Top TL for 4th quarter of 2015
- > Top TL for 1st quarter of 2016
- > Top Agent for 2014 Fiscal awarded in Singapore
- ➤ Top Agent for 3rd quarter of 2014
- > Team Leader onboarding certificate facilitated by Tessa Salandanan, Regional Development Leader.

Familiar with Tools such as:

- > Asana, Trello and Slack
- Canva, Photoshop and Vidnami
- > Jungle Scout, Helium 10, Viral Launch and Rebate Key
- ManyChat, ClickFunnels, Active Campaign
- Google Spreadsheet and Excel

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Bachelor of Science in Management University of Caloocan (2005 – 2009)

Roosevelt, Quezon City

Cantilan National High School (2001 – 2005)

Cantilan, Surigao del Sur Mindanao

N.A.U.M.E.S elementary School (1994-2001)

Cantilan, Surigao del Sur Mindanao